Rohit Sahu

Web Developer

Web Developer with 2+ years of experience in designing and developing user interfaces, testing, debugging. I've extensive experience using multiple standard programming languages. Proven ability in optimizing web functionalities that improve data retrieval and workflow efficiencies.



- 🔀 rohitsahu728@gmail.com
- Guwahati, India
- in linkedin.com/in/rohit-sahu-62043615a
- f facebook.com/rernr
- istackoverflow.com/users/12099177/rohit-sahu

- +918402081401
- rohit52594.github.io
- S rohit52594@outlook.com
- github.com/rohit52594
- medium.com/@rohitsahu728

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Odometry Technix

04/2019 - Present

Guwahati

Working as a Web Developer with React, Node.js, PHP. Growing here with learning and using tools like AWS, Firebase, Codeigniter, Laravel, React using Hooks, Node.js, etc.

Intern

DiTech Process Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

11/2018 - 03/2019

Guwahati

Done Internship here as On Job Trainee. Learned working with XHTML, CSS3 for making EPUB's and working with XML files, document management, etc.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology

Nazira College 06/2015 - 12/2018

Nazira, Sivasagar

Courses

 The primary subjects are: C, C++, Java, PHP, MySQL, Vanilla JavaScript, jQuery, Database Management System, Software development and Web Development

Microsoft Certified Systems Expert ATL Infosys

09/2018 - 02/2019

Guwahati

Courses

 The primary topics in MCSE (Microsoft Certified Systems Expert) are: Windows Server. Active Directory Installation, DHCP, IP Addressing, LAN Configuration, Group Policy Object & OU.

SKILLS

React.js AWS PHP Node.js Linux

AOP/OOP MaterialUI jQuery Git SSH

Express.js

PROJECTS

onor.world

Used React.js and admin panel in Core UI.

takenstar.com

Used react redux with express in backend.

sunbingo90.com

Tambola game front-end developed in react.js

buysara.com

E-commerce application developed in Codeigniter

patidarrangcollege.com

Admission portal developed in Codeigniter

Others

 Some other projects such as Inventory Management, MLM, CMS, booking portals etc.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Web Developer (07/2015 - 06/2016) - NAASCOM Junior Web Developer from NSQF Level 5

LANGUAGES

Hindi English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency Professional Working Proficiency

Assamese

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Listening to Music Cooking Coding Travelling

Video Games